[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which film did Pywackett appear?", "correct_answer": "Bell, Book and Candle", "incorrect_answers": ["The Cats in the Cradle", "The Golden Cat of Atlantis", "Old Possums Books of Cats"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these medical conditions is caused by the ricin found in castor beans?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Death", "Severe diarrhea", "Long term organ damage"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the explorer The Goonies find in the caves in the self-titled movie?", "correct_answer": "Chester Copperpot", "incorrect_answers": ["Chester Copperfield", "Charlie Copperfield", "Charlie Copperpot"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Name the prehistoric reptile of the late Jurassic and Cretaceous period with featherless wing membrane.  It is believed this reptile flew.", "correct_answer": "Pterodactyl", "incorrect_answers": ["Bronchialsaurus", "Accipitridae Raptor", "dactylic raptor"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of the following determines to which chemical element a certain atom belongs?", "correct_answer": "The number of protons", "incorrect_answers": ["The number of electrons", "The number of neutrons", "None of these"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In Blazing Saddles, the townspeople of Rock Ridge did not want to give any land at first to which minority group?", "correct_answer": "The Irish", "incorrect_answers": ["The Italians", "The Blacks", "The Chinese"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In the year 100, there were about 255 square miles per living person on earth. What was that number in  2000?", "correct_answer": "8.2 square miles", "incorrect_answers": ["17.3 square  miles", "127.4 square miles", "64.1 square  miles"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In which time zone(s) would you find the state of Florida?", "correct_answer": "Eastern and Central", "incorrect_answers": ["Central", "Central and Mountain", "Eastern"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1964 Francis Cardinal Spellman banned all Catholic children in the New York Archdiocese from doing this.", "correct_answer": "Doing the Twist", "incorrect_answers": ["Watching too much TV", "Watching Elvis Presley", "Listening to transistor radios in school"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Which of these is not the equivalent of what Americans often call head cheese?", "correct_answer": "Kumiss", "incorrect_answers": ["Brawn", "Brabant", "Sylta"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Every summer, a special basketball tournament is held in Harlem, NY.  What is the original name of the tournament?", "correct_answer": "The Rucker Tournament", "incorrect_answers": ["The Harlem Five on Five", "The Entertainers Basketball Classic", "The Holcombe Tournament"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "A pair of fair dice are rolled and the numbers on the dice are added. What is the probability that you will roll a seven?", "correct_answer": "6 out of 36", "incorrect_answers": ["7 out of 36", "13 out of 36", "2 out of 6"]}]